♪ I wish everyday could be ♪
♪ Christmas day ♪
♪ There would be no war ♪
♪ Just peace ♪
♪ And all around the world ♪
♪ Celebrate our differences ♪
♪ No matter what your religion is ♪
♪ I wish that we could live our lives ♪
♪ In harmony ♪
♪ Three hundred and sixty-five ♪
♪ Days of peace ♪
♪ Celebrate our differences ♪
♪ No matter what your religion is ♪
♪ If I only had one wish ♪
♪ That wish would be ♪
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ If I only had one gift ♪
♪ I'd give this to ♪
♪ Every boy and every girl ♪
♪ Fa la la la-la ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm ♪
♪ Watch the children as they play ♪
♪ So innocent ♪
♪ Gives me hope we'll see the day ♪
♪ When we can learn ♪
♪ To love each other ♪
♪ Like we're sister ♪
♪ Like we're brother ♪
♪ If I only had one wish ♪
♪ That wish would be ♪
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ And if I only had one gift ♪
♪ I'd give this to ♪
♪ Every boy and every girl ♪
♪ Fa la la la-la... ♪
I know I'm new in town,
but Poppy's Petals
has been a staple in Santa Mesa
for nearly two decades.
I-I know I'm not Gladys,
but she was my grandma,
and she did name the shop
after me.
Everything I know,
I learned from her.
Well, I just know
that my flowers
will make your tea party
perfectly pristine.
Well, I was thinking
something elegant
and monochromatic.
Maybe some white poinsettias
and some, uh,
silver-painted lemon leaves.
And if you wanna add
a little character,
we could get
some anti-crystal vases.
Uh-huh.
Oh! Okay.
Okay, well, I really hope
I hear from you.
Thank you,
Mrs. Darington.
You okay?
Uh, yeah.
Thank you. I'm-I'm just
bit of a klutz.
Well, at least your phone's
in a protective case.
Ah, yeah. Thank you.
Those, uh, pine sprigs
are great,
but they'll break on you
if you're not careful with them.
Well, I'm-I'm just
not very good at multitasking.
I had to go on foot today.
Sounds like you need
a delivery van.
- I'm, I'm Garrett.
- I'm Poppy.
Yeah, I actually have one.
She's just a little cranky
today, that's all.
Well, maybe, Santa can get you
a new van for Christmas.
Oh, my Edna is irreplaceable.
But I do have a long list
of things I need from Santa.
You have a van named Edna?
If you saw her,
you would understand.
Okay. Uh...
Well, if Edna has to stay
then what else
is on the top of your, uh,
Christmas wish list?
Well, besides getting somewhere
on time for once, um...
No, no, no, no.
That's time management.
I was asking about a wish.
Okay, well,
I really like churros.
Now we're talking.
I just happen to know a place
on the East side
that has the best churros
in all of Santa Mesa.
Okay, well, uh,
I'll have to
check it out sometime.
Um, can I give you a hint?
I'm down that way, but, uh,
I'm happy to help out
for a few minute
in the spirit
of the giving season.
Oh, you're, uh...
Thank you. I'm okay.
I'll survive,
even if the sprigs don't.
- Thank you, though.
- All right.
Well, uh, good luck
with the multitasking, Poppy.
It was nice meeting you.
You, too, um...
- Garrett.
- Merry Christmas.
- You, too.
So, how did the call go?
Did we get it?
She's considering her options.
We're an untried entity.
Look, I know that Santa Mesa
can be a little snooty,
but I promise you, you just get
one of these Country Club
tea party ladies in your pocket
and we are set and pretty.
- I'm trying.
- You'll get it.
- I hope so.
- You kinda have to.
We just got the electric bill.
And we really gotta update
this flower cooler.
It is sucking down kilowatts
like there's no tomorrow.
Okay. Well, my grandma opened
this shop with that cooler.
Which is precisely why it's long
overdue for its retirement.
I feel like all we do
is pay bills.
Or not pay bills.
I just wanna make pretty things
and make people happy.
And that is a noble
and highly under-appreciated
calling.
Listen, all of this
is gonna blossom real soon.
- I promise you.
- I hope so.
I really don't wanna
let my grandma down.
- Good morning, ladies.
- Morning.
Looks lovely.
Okay, I am off
to the nursing home.
Poppy, you can't be
doing that anymore.
But it makes the residents
so happy
to see pretty flowers,
and, Natalie,
it's three weeks till Christmas.
They deserve some holiday cheer.
And we need
some paying customers.
You can't give
all the flowers away.
My mother always said
you have to give the world
what you want it
to give back to you.
So you want the world to give
you free flowers for life?
No. I wanna be happy,
so I give away happy.
That's what Christmas
is about, right?
I wish someone would pay you
to come up
with inspirational posters.
Ooh, side hustle.
Let's think about it.
Come on!
Come on.
Oh, I know it's early, Edna,
but, please, come on.
I'm on my way.
Where you at?
The front of the shop.
Okay, don't go anywhere.
Very cute.
Edna...
- Poppy, I hate to say it...
- Then don't.
- This is just a Band-Aid.
- Well, that's not bad news.
I mean, Band-Aids are like
a medical marvel, right?
Poppy, this old gal's
on her last leg.
Yeah, well, she's gonna have to
get a crutch
because this old girl
is cash-poor.
Well, this'll last you
a couple of weeks, at most.
Where's your faith, Joe?
The faith in me is charming,
but I'm a mechanic,
not Santa Claus.
Uh, Pops, I love Edna, too...
but I think it's time
to let her go.
Okay. I'm going back in.
Hey, do you want me to order you
something for lunch?
Hey, I might go out today.
You don't know.
So, "Turkey club,
hold the cheese, add avocado?"
Yeah, you know what?
Let's add bacon today.
I'm feeling adventurous.
- Okay.
- Oh, oh! Marie.
Uh, these... are for you.
Merry Christmas
to the best assistant ever.
Second row to The Nutcracker?
Thank you. How did you...
I heard you talking to Justine
about how your boyfriend
wouldn't spring for tickets.
I want you to enjoy the show.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Merry Christmas.
Mrs. Darington called
while you were out on delivery.
Okay, this is the part
where you smile
and clap your hands
and throw confetti
and say, "We got the gig."
I... could do
the first three things
if you want.
She said they're going
with Covington Designs.
Ugh! Gosh.
You know what I would really
like for Christmas?
To never hear the word
"Covington Designs" again.
Good luck with that.
Why doesn't anyone want anything
fresh and new in this town?
Do you want the truth
or should I just wait,
see where this goes?
Every time I lose a gig,
it's because it goes
to Covington Designs.
Well, at least she let us know.
I mean, she could have
kept us waiting, hoping, right?
Uh, I prefer hoping,
because it's...
you know, hopeful.
Hey, it is dogwood eats dogwood
in the cut-throat world
of flower arranging.
But there's no time for tears
because you have
another delivery.
Twelve dozen long-stem roses.
Classic, romantic
and profitable.
- In the name of romance.
- And profits.
We carry on.
No, Edna, please.
No. Edna, please.
Not today.
Just one more delivery.
Come on.
Okay.
Hey, this is Joe.
Leave a message.
Hey, Joe, it's Poppy.
I'm on the corner of...
First and Hannover.
The old girl is having
another flare up.
Could you come quick?
Thank you.
Oh, Edna.
Is this a sign?
Am I just supposed to give up?
"Five thousand dollars?"
This is a sign.
Ah... Yes?
What did you wanna talk about?
Blair, we have been
working together
for 12 years now.
Oh, darling,
did I forget out anniversary?
Forgive me,
I've just been flooded
with these designs for
the governor's Christmas ball.
Now, I have been with you since
you started Covington Designs
and along the way I've gotten
a few offers here and there.
Some enticing.
But I've always believed
in your vision.
Too much sentimentality.
And all before noon.
Now, part of what
has kept me here
is the promise that one day
I might see my name
above that door, too.
Ah, yes.
As we reflect on the past,
we also dream about the future.
Well, that time is now, Blair.
Time for what?
Time for you
to make me a partner.
And you said this would happen
last year after the holidays.
And, yet, here we are again,
and nothing's changed.
What gives?
Garrett, you know
my intentions are good,
but you can't just come in here
and waylay me in the middle
of a design session.
I tried to talk to you about it
all the time
throughout the year,
but there's always some excuse.
You're too busy.
It's not an excuse. It's true.
Listen, if you can't give me
a clear timeline for partnership
then I have to consider
other options.
Don't pout. We'll come up
with an agreement.
I'm serious, Blair.
Listen, I appreciate
everything you've done.
You know that.
But I won't stay in
for less than what I deserve.
That's why I'll give you
until tomorrow to decide.
And if not?
You'll have to accept
my resignation.
I think I found a solution
to our problem.
Ooh, did Santa sent us a sleigh
with eight million tiny dollars?
I am gonna win at the Santa Mesa
Holiday Floral Show.
First prize is $5,000.
Can you imagine the press?
Poppy, I hate to
burst your bubble,
but there is only one winner
of the Santa Mesa
Holiday Floral Show,
and that is Blair Covington.
I thought we said that we're
never gonna say that name again.
She's taken top prize
for 12 years running.
Nobody can beat her.
Nobody, except a young,
upstart, new,
and ready to take
on the flower world by storm.
Do you have any idea
what you're in for?
Sit.
Okay, so if you were selected
as one of the ten top entries,
the next three weeks
of your life
are going to be consumed
by a holiday flower explosion.
Three insanely intense rounds
of competition
with the grand finale unfolding
at the convention center.
- On Christmas Eve's eve.
- What?
The day before,
the day before Christmas.
Fine. I'm in.
Where do I send my look book?
I am loving
this can-do attitude.
I'm gonna go spruce up
your entry letter.
I'm gonna win this flower show.
Wait, did you start without me?
Oh, just the lights.
I saved the ornaments for you.
Oh.
Is that my pipe cleaner Santa?
You know, I remember when you
brought that home from school.
You were so proud of it.
And your mom's best guess was
it was a reindeer.
And I burst into tears
and threw it in the trash.
Yeah, but she found it,
she put it
right in the middle of the tree,
where everyone could see it.
- Every single year.
- Yeah.
You know, your mom always said
that you inherited
your grandmother's
creative genius.
Yeah, well, I hope
that's the truth
if I'm gonna win the Santa Mesa
Holiday Floral Show.
- You're entering?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, honey, that's wonderful.
Congratulations.
Yeah.
You know, your mom
would be so proud of you
taking over the family shop
and...
Well, I don't know
what I would have done
if you weren't around
to help me.
Well, first of all,
you'd starve.
What? Dad, I can cook.
Not buttered, toasted
PB and J's.
Oof! That doesn't count.
Who doesn't like
peanut butter and jelly?
Your palate
is just underdeveloped.
Oh, really?
Well, we'll see what you have to
say after you've had twobowls
of my absolutely,
amazingly delicious chili.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, one sec.
Okay.
Now it's really Christmas.
Yeah.
Now, if we could
just get some snow.
Did we?
You got in.
I'm so excited.
Okay, but seriously,
we have so much work to do.
- Are you ready?
- I was born ready.
Yes!
Well, I'd like to say
congrats to us
for getting into
the Holiday Floral Show
again this year.
But I mean,
was it ever really a question?
Nope.
Oh, these are nice.
Let's switch out
the, uh, paperwhites
for some amborellas.
It's just more grand.
Are these for an event?
No, it's for the show.
I design
the Holiday Floral Show.
This is your opportunity
to let me step forward.
Come on, your name
will still be on the booth.
Yeah, that's the problem.
It's my name and myreputation
that's at stake here.
Maybe next year when you've had
more time to prepare.
These designs are great
and you know it, Blair.
I don't know what your hurry is.
I mean, Garrett, it's not like
you aren't deeply embedded
in this company
with a very generous salary.
Okay, Blair...
I wanna make a deal with you.
I don't make deals.
I make decisions.
Let me design the entrees
into the floral show this year.
Okay?
Just give me control,
and if I win...
you make me partner.
You put my name above the door.
And if I lose...
I'll sign a contract to work
with you for five years
in any capacity you see fit.
And if I say no?
I walk.
I'd be starting from scratch,
but you and I both know
I'd have no problem
making a name for myself
in this town.
Well, your confidence
is inspiring.
Don't disappoint me.
Yes!
Hello?
Dad, what're you doing here?
Well, I was just
driving on my way home
and, uh, I saw the lights
were still on and...
- You're here late.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I just want everything
to be perfect for the show,
so I'm trying
to get ahead of the game.
Well, I brought you
some edible assistance.
Little hot cocoa...
and Christmas cookies.
Thank you, dad.
- May I see?
- Yeah.
So the theme for the first round
is Christmas is fun the happy.
I'm doing an Edwardian fireplace
with hung stockings.
- What do you think?
- Well, I think it's perfect.
I was hoping for a bit more
constructive criticism, dad.
Well, I'm afraid
you've come to the wrong guy,
because I happen to think
that everything you do
is just genius.
Dad, I need to win this show.
I don't know how much longer
I can keep this place afloat.
Well, you know
I'll do anything to help.
It's just all these bills
keep piling up
while everything else
is breaking down.
Poppy, let me give you
some money.
No, dad, I wanna do this
on my own.
Well, then we'll make it a loan.
Dad, I'm not letting you dip
into your retirement fund.
You've already done enough.
Poppy, it's what parents do.
Look, I take care of you,
and then someday
when I'm really old,
hopefully, you won't put me
in any of those
tacky Christmas sweater vests.
Okay.
Tsk. Thank you, dad. I love you.
You're gonna come out on top
because you always do.
I hope so.
This store depends on it.
Oh, my phone.
Oh! I'm so... Excuse me.
Sorry about that.
Hey, it's you again.
Wow, you should really hire
an intern
to help you
with your multitasking.
I feel like I'm in one of those
hidden camera shows
and eventually
I'm gonna find out.
I just have brilliant
comedic timing.
Uh...
Ooh, I'm-I'm sorry,
I'm running late.
No. No problem. Me, too.
Uh, I'm surprised
to see you here.
What, with my undying love
for pine sprigs.
Is it really that implausible?
No, I'm just usually
not that lucky.
Listen, I'd offer to help you
carry this,
but I got a feeling
I already know the answer.
Yeah. One day, I'll learn.
I hope I'm there when you do.
I forgot my phone,
so I'm going back that way.
Okay. All right,
I'll see you around.
- Okay.
- Poppy.
Hmm, why does he have to be
so handsome?
That's Poppy,
from Poppy's Petals.
- I think I met a guy.
- Ooh, do tell.
I've run into him twice now...
Oh, wait, dad, just...
Um, left hangin'
in suspense much?
Poppy, tell me more.
Oh, wow,
that is an impressive costume.
Oh, well, at Covington Designs
we like to take
every opportunity
to further the assigned theme.
Oh, you work
at Covington Designs.
I heard they're
pretty big winners.
But you better tell
that Blair Covington
there is a new sheriff
in flower town.
What have you heard
about Blair Covington?
What haven't I heard?
By the way, is she here yet?
I would love
you to point her out.
Just to size up my competition.
I am Blair Covington.
Hi.
Um, and if you want my advice,
I'd, uh, thin out
the pepper berries.
- Thank you so much.
- Mm.
So that went well.
Get me the pepper berries.
Right.
Mm. Mmm.
What do you think?
Tsk...
Well...
I suppose...
we'll have to let
the judges decide.
I take that
as a vote of confidence.
Hmm.
Good afternoon, judges.
Miss Cromwell-Eastland.
Welcome to our Edwardian
Christmas party.
Hello.
I am certain you will find
everything here
up to the exacting standards
of what you'd expect
from the Fountains Abbey Estate.
Lovely.
Oh, Poppy's Petals.
I have passed your store before.
It is so cute.
Oh, thank you.
- Catchy name, too.
- Oh.
- Phil and Audrey Wilson.
- Hi!
- Roses Are Red Florals.
- Hi.
- Bart.
- Nice to meet you.
- Natalie.
- Hi. Pleasure.
Team's lookin' a little thin,
don't you think?
Um, you know what?
Best of luck to you guys.
We'll see you.
She's the mayor's daughter.
Can you get me my phone?
Yeah.
- Hey, Poppy.
- Joe?
- She break down again?
- No, no, no. Edna's fine.
But I need you.
Could you come down here?
- On my way.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Guys. Guys.
- Mm.
Hi, uh, Poppy's Petals.
Enchanting.
Total engine rebuild.
Rush job. Got here
as quick as I could.
Thank you so much, Joe,
apparently, our team
was looking a little thinner
than the everyone else's.
Not a problem. I got
nothing better going on now.
It's always a good time to stop
and smell the roses. Right?
And, yet, he shows up
covered in grease.
Oh, thanks.
Always a pleasure, Nat.
Welcome
to the Santa Mesa Holiday
Floral Show preliminary
competition.
I am Dorothy Cromwell-Eastland.
And as many of you know,
I am the chairwoman
of the Santa Mesa
Floral Beautification Committee.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
You are far too kind.
And now, without further ado,
it is time to announce
today's top five designers
who will advance
to the semi-finals
in one week.
And our first semi-finalist,
Poppy Benson of Poppy's Petals.
Congratulations.
Our second designer,
Garrett Hurley
of Covington Designs.
Next up,
Phil and Audrey Wilson
of Roses Are Red Florals.
Please come to the stage.
Congratulations to all of you.
What a delight.
So you're the real deal, huh?
- And now...
- I'm sorry?
I mean, you have your own shop
and everything.
I didn't realize you were
actually a floral designer.
Okay, come on,
how many times have you seen me
trip and pick up
foliage and flowers?
I thought maybe you were
at some holiday party.
Or you could be
someone's assistant.
So, you work
for Blair Covington?
She's my mentor.
Apparently,
she's everyone's mentor.
- Huh?
- Lastly...
We are so thrilled to announce
that this year
our semi-final theme
will be...
Drumroll, please.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
The Twelve Days Of Christmas.
Listen, it was very nice
to meet you.
I just wanna let you know
that I plan on winning
this entire shebang.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you,
but not only
do I plan on winning,
I am going to win.
Okay, fine.
- Hello again.
- Hi.
I heard your presentation
was a big hit.
Uh, yeah, it's, uh,
half-packed up now.
- I'm really sorry I missed it.
- Oh, it's okay.
Oh, here. Here's some holly
as a consolation.
Ooh.
Nice outfit, by the way.
How did you get here?
- In a horse and carriage?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, well, we really try to...
- Further the theme. Oh.
- Further the theme. Yes.
Blair mentioned that
to me earlier
when she was mentoring me
on how to design my booth.
Well, she does have
a very keen eye.
I mean, I wouldn't
totally discount her advice.
You're really Team Blair,
aren't you?
Twelve years and counting.
That said, it helps
she is the biggest name
in the flower game in this town.
Well, seeing as
we're sworn enemies, I mean,
do you think we should even be
having this conversation?
I might unearth some invaluable
trade secrets.
I don't know,
I feel like you and I
can still be friends, right?
We have enough in common.
Ah, a fellow love of flowers
is not necessarily
a fine friend to make.
Well, how about
a fellow love of churros?
And of costume design?
And of Christmas?
How about a conflict
of interest?
Ooh, looks like
you're being beckoned.
Right. Wish me luck.
I'll see you tomorrow
at the press conference?
Okay.
- Was that a yes?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Wow.
This is the real deal, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I am so sorry, honey,
but your hair is not ready
for primetime.
- We really should...
- It's fine. Just leave it.
I believe in the power
of good hair.
Okay, fine,
just at least put this in,
so you have some sparkle.
Wait, there's that guy.
The cute guy
I was telling you about.
- Ooh, show me.
- Don't look, he's gonna see you.
Garrett Hurley.
The cute guy that works
for Covington Designs?
No. He had potential
to be good, right?
Well, who says
this isn't giving good?
Natalie, I don't need
the drama right now.
I need to focus
on the competition.
Well, I'd take out
a loan to cash in
on that kind of distraction.
Oh, my gosh. He saw me looking.
Hey, think like a winner.
But like a, a fragrant winner.
Ugh! Stop, stop doing it.
Welcome to the madness.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Wasn't expecting all these
reporters to be here.
Oh, the flower show
in Santa Mesa is a big deal.
I mean, people go nuts for this.
Blair is certainly
in her element.
Isn't she stealing your thunder?
Nah, it's good for the company.
I don't really mind.
Yeah. Same here.
Hey, listen, Poppy,
um, just so you know,
I kinda have to win
this competition.
Yeah, same here.
No, you don't,
you don't understand.
Blair and I have an agreement,
so... have to do it.
And I need to get a new cooler,
so looks like
we're in the same boat.
But I... Oh, wow,
are you wearing a new perfume?
Poppy! Garrett!
This is Jessica Abbott
from Channel 15.
I think you should speak
with her about this competition
between the new girl
and the old guard.
Ah.
Picture time.
Beautiful.
Merry Christmas.
I brought my best friend
a healthy holiday breakfast.
Croissants and...
Peanut butter
with a side of jam.
You are jam...
I mean, you're a gem.
Wow. It is a little too early
for bad jokes.
Clearly, I haven't gotten out
lately,
so this looks amazing.
Thank you.
So, how's all the hubbub
with the flower show?
Ugh! Exhausting.
And how's Blair handling
you being in charge?
Begrudgingly.
And you really
gonna go in a deal with her?
I mean, it's now or never,
right?
It's just like,
five years is a long time
to be doing something
you don't wanna do.
Yeah, but you know what?
That part of the bet
doesn't really matter
because I am going to win.
So I saw you on the local news
last night
with that cute competitor.
She is totally your type.
Is she?
See? I knew it.
- What?
- You did the eyebrow thing.
That thing you do when you think
a girl's cute.
Excuse me?
The eyebrow doesn't lie.
I've known you my whole life.
Okay, fine. But you know what?
Even if there was a spark,
I'm pretty sure
she'd be standing by
with a bucket of water
to put it out.
Come on, you're cute,
and charming,
and you cook, and clean,
and do your own laundry.
I mean, what more
could a gal want?
So, I guess she inherited her
flower shop
from her grandmother,
like, six months ago,
and... it's not doing so well.
So, I assume she's gonna use the
winnings to keep things afloat.
- Complicated indeed.
- Yeah.
I mean, basically,
if I win everything I want
she loses everything she wants.
Well, what if I told you
I could help you out
with your romantic endeavors?
What are you talking about?
Well, mother's
Annual Christmas Fete
is coming up,
and we need to hire a florist.
We'd usually use that
Garrett what's-his-name,
but, uh, I heard there's
a new up-and-coming florist
who might be worth a shot.
Tiffany Daniels,
you are a peach.
And the best friend anybody
could ever ask for.
How can I ever repay you?
Insanely expensive shoes
for my birthday
will do just fine.
Okay.
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, bye.
Guess who just booked a big gig.
Blair Covington?
Too soon? I'm kidding,
I'm kidding.
I'm so excited.
Tell me everything.
Okay, so it's a massive
society Christmas party
with a 150 invites,
and they want center pieces
for all the tables.
Oh, we're gonna need
a big order.
No, huge order. Giant order.
I was told, "Spare no expense."
My three favorite words
in the English language.
Oh, um, are we gonna have time
to do both?
- Both?
- Hello.
The semi-finals round
of the competition
is tomorrow.
Oh, of course. I'm all over it.
When there's a will,
there's a way.
Now that's the Christmas spirit.
Okay, so about this
society party,
I was thinking
we should do something modern
like, I've been wanting to use
Indonesian eucalyptus.
What do you think?
International flair. I like.
Yeah. Maybe, like, with some
Christmassy red ombre flowers.
Yes. Poppy, that is it.
You're in.
And in celebration of this
very momentous moment...
I'm gonna pay the electric bill.
Yes!
I thought you were coming
as a little drummer boy.
You know, I don't think
I need to wear a costume.
I feel like the design
speaks for itself.
Careful attention
to the theme...
is part of the reason
that Covington Designs
has won this flower show
for the last 12 years.
Is there nothing to be said
for tradition?
I understand that
it's your tradition, Blair,
but I thought you said we could
try things my way
this time around.
I do wish the best for you,
Garrett.
But I must admit
that it's things like this that
do cause my confidence to waver.
Look, I need you to understand
I was taught by the best.
But now it's time for the master
to let her pupil shine.
Fine. Fine.
But you better shine.
Poppy, we're gonna get a drink.
Do you want something?
- No, I'm okay. Thanks, dad.
- Yeah? Okay.
Nat?
Hello there, fellow competitor.
You're so formal.
Yes, well, we are
very professional
over here at Poppy's Petals.
Okay. Well, uh, I'm sorry
to interrupt.
I, I just wanted to see
if my friend Tiffany called.
You know Tiffany Daniels?
Yeah. Yeah, her mom's throwing
this big Christmas party,
and we're kinda swamped,
so, um...
I just mentioned your name.
You sent me the referral.
- Is that bad?
- No, it's...
Well, it's just weird that you
are supporting your competitor.
Oh, come on, we don't have
to compete outside the show.
I suppose not, I...
I just don't know what to say.
I'm sorry, did I,
did I screw up?
No, no, not at all.
It's actually very sweet.
Thank you.
Well, look, um, maybe you'll
agree to have dinner with me
after the show?
Say yes.
Uh, what would Blair say?
Well, I'm more interested
to know what you would say.
Just say yes.
Yeah. Just say yes.
It... I don't know.
It just, it just feels
very complicated.
Okay, well, how's this? Um...
If we both make it
to the finals,
we'll go have dinner together
to celebrate.
- I'm so going to the finals.
- Great. So am I.
Done. Okay.
- I'm looking forward to dinner.
- Yes!
Ah. Stop.
- What? I didn't do any...
- You stop it.
Oh, dear.
Good evening,
and welcome, one and all,
to the Santa Mesa
Holiday Floral Show
semi-final competition.
We have had an amazing day
of flowers
and holiday cheer,
ladies and gentlemen.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
I believe the theme
could easily have been
Holiday Floral Fashion
At Its Finest.
Let's give all these designers
a huge round of applause.
And before we announce
our top three finalists,
I am pleased to announce
that theme of this year's
flower grand finale
in one week will be
Alice in a Winter Wonderland.
Prepare to be enchanted.
And now, the moment
you've been waiting for.
Our top three
contending finalists
in no particular order.
Audrey and Phil Wilson
of Roses Are Red Florals.
Our second finalist is...
Garrett Hurley
of Covington Designs.
And our third and last finalist
for this year's
Santa Mesa Holiday Floral Show
is...
Poppy Benson of Poppy's Petals.
So, looks we have a celebratory
dinner tonight.
It appears we do.
Here's my card with my mobile.
Just text me your address.
Maybe 7 o'clock?
Let me just check my schedule.
Yeah. It should be fine.
- Yeah? Great.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Poppy, you did great.
- And you got a date.
- It's not a date.
Oh, it is totally a date.
A date?
- Hey, Garrett. Come on in.
- Hey, Mr. Benson.
Ah, that's a good-looking tree.
Have a seat.
So, as the father of,
uh, the girl
you're about to take on a date,
I have to ask.
I-is this an attempt to, uh,
shake down the enemy?
For inside information?
No, sir. Not at all.
Oh, good. Because I'd hate for
my daughter to be disappointed.
You know, if your intentions
weren't on the up and up.
Oh, I-I-I have, I had no plans
o-of disappointing her
in, in any way, sir.
I-I assure you.
So, what are your intentions?
Well, as, as it relates
to dinner,
uh, it's purely, a date-related.
I mean, I mean, the dinner's not
a professional date,
it's more of a personal...
nature.
You know, the truth is, I just
think your daughter's great.
And honestly, I just wanna get
to know her better, that's all.
Well, I am glad
we cleared this up.
How about a drink, Garrett?
Eggnog?
Uh...
I'm good. I appreciate it.
Okay. Well, how about water?
'Cause you're kinda
breaking a little sweat.
Yeah. I'm feeling a little...
Water sounds good.
Okay, then. I'll be right back.
That wedding picture
is my grandparents.
This used to be their house.
I got you a cookie bouquet.
I figured you can't get enough
florist flowers, right?
Well, thank you.
It's, it's very sweet.
You look beautiful.
Oh, uh, thanks.
So, how old are you
in this photo?
Uh... I was eight years old.
- And that's your mom?
- Mm-hmm.
Gosh. You really got her eyes.
Yeah, apparently,
I have her green thumb, too,
which she inherited
from my grandma.
Come see. This, uh...
This was my mom's garden.
It was amazing.
She had all these wild flowers
and climbing vines
and butterflies and roses.
Really magical.
Had a lot of fairy tale princess
adventures in there.
That sounds beautiful.
Yeah. Maybe I'll recreate it
some day.
You should.
It'd be like going on
a whole new adventure.
Yeah, maybe.
I come bearing hydration
and eggnog.
- Hey.
- Uh, thank you, dad.
But we actually
have to get going.
That's right.
I made a reservation at 7:30.
- So...
- Okay, fine.
Um, but don't stay out too late.
You have a big day of making
arrangements tomorrow. Yes?
Okay. Yes, I do. Okay.
All right, I assure you.
I will have her back
at a reasonable hour.
All right. Thank you.
Okay. You kids have a good time.
Hope it doesn't get too cold.
You warm?
- I'm good. Thank you.
- Great.
So, is your dad usually
an eggnog drinker?
Okay. I-I'm sorry.
My dad just texted me.
The good news is he likes you.
I am so sorry he grilled you.
I had nothing to do with that.
That's okay. He was fine.
It was fine.
I think he's just concerned
with how invested you are
with Covington, that's all.
Am I?
I don't know.
I-I guess I get it.
I'm just, uh, I'm torn sometimes
between my obligations
and my passions, that's all.
What do you mean?
I just mean I...
There's a lot...
There's a lot I have left
I want to achieve.
Well, I'm sure you will,
because you're very talented.
Whoa.
Was that a compliment?
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
I've been really harsh.
I... I just have so much to lose
in this competition.
Don't we all?
You know, maybe
there's... some way
in which we all end up winning
at the end of this, you think?
Well, if you have
any suggestions,
I'm open to hearing them.
Or maybe we can just hope
that everyone's Christmas wishes
come true.
Well, sharing this evening
with you has certainly been
getting things off
to a good start.
No, no, no. I..
Let me, I insist.
Oh, can I, please? You already
got me the Country Club gig.
I-I can get this. Please...
My pleasure. Tell you what.
Why don't you treat me
to a dessert,
and then we'll call it even?
Dessert?
Okay. Thank you.
This place is so cute.
It's very Christmassy.
It isvery Christmassy.
- Good coffee, good desserts.
- Oh.
Oh, so, I was thinking
of using Indonesian eucalyptus
for Tiffany's mom's party.
I want the center pieces
to be very edgy.
Edgy flowers, huh?
That's very rock and roll
of you.
Are you questioning
my rock and roll?
I would never question
a lady's rock and roll.
It's very unchivalrous of me.
Seriously though,
your passion's really inspiring.
I mean it, it-it's really clear
that you love what you do.
- Can we have two?
- I mean, what's not to love?
I mean, my job is to make
people's lives pretty.
Yeah, that's a really great way
if think about it.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yum.
You know, sometimes,
I feel like I get
just too caught up
in the business side of things.
Oh, don't feel bad.
It's hard to get caught up
in business,
especially when you don't
have a lot of business.
Thank you.
You're really talented
at what you do, Poppy.
You know that?
Your grandmother knew
what she was doing
when she gave you the shop.
Thank you.
What about you?
Do you, um, plan on staying
at Covington Design?
You know, I owe Blair a lot.
I mean, kinda my whole career.
Does it mean she owns you?
Well, we're in negotiations
about my, my future
at the company.
But I think
after the flower show...
maybe some big change
is in store.
You mean, after
I win the flower show.
Well, if you play it like that
then I amgonna question
your rock and roll.
Lady or no lady,
the gloves are comin' off.
Um...
Okay.
Hey, can we have two espressos,
please?
So, what got you
into floral design?
Well, after I graduated
from college,
I got a master's degree in both
Architecture and Business.
And then I became
Blair's assistant.
- Her assistant?
- Yeah.
Yeah. All-all the places
I applied to for jobs
thought I was over-qualified.
And I didn't have job.
I needed one.
And so, she took a chance on me
when no one else would.
Wasn't expecting to hear that.
Yeah. She, she and my mom
are old friends.
And so, you know, I thought
she'd be a good place to start,
and then I'd move along
to something bigger and better,
but she was working a...
a wedding for a friend, solo
and she got in
way over her head.
Blair Covington in over head?
I find that hard to believe.
Well, believe it.
Yeah, she first had me doing
the boy's boutonnieres.
And I guess she was impressed
with what I did there,
and so, then she, you know,
had me do
the flower arrangements
in the foyer.
And, yeah, after a while,
we both kinda realized
not only was it something
I was good at,
but, you know, something
I kinda love doing.
That's amazing.
Yeah, well, you know,
arranging flowers
is all architecture.
I've always kinda had an eye
for symmetry and...
and design and...
I don't know, you know,
maybe I could use a little
of what I learned
in grad school.
Anyways,
the rest is just history.
I've been with her ever since.
I just assumed Covington Designs
had been around forever.
Well, there was once in time
when Blair Covington
was the new florist in town.
Just like you.
She worked hard for her success.
We both did.
So, what, you just pulled up
your bootstraps
made a couple boutonnieres
and now
you're the best-dressed florist
in town?
Easy as that?
Yeah. Just sitting
at a candlelit table,
drinking an espresso
with the most beautiful florist
in town.
It's as simple as that.
Cheers.
- Okay, this is it.
- Wow.
You are officially
behind enemy lines.
What do you think?
It's really cute.
It's exactly what I thought
your shop would look like.
I'm just gonna
get these sketches.
I can't believe I left them.
Okay. Oh!
Oh, could I maybe interest you
in one of our lovely
Christmas arrangements?
Maybe something sophisticated
and, and charming?
Only if I can help.
I'm pretty particular
about my arrangements.
Oh. Uh...
Okay.
Well, um, why don't we see
what happens
when the new girl
and the old guard join forces?
Okay.
♪ I don't know what it is ♪
♪ About this time of year ♪
♪ Once the cold sets in ♪
♪ And then the mind is clear ♪
♪ That it's Christmas time ♪
♪ You should be here with me ♪
♪ Got your stocking hanging ♪
♪ By the mistletoe ♪
♪ Where we should be kissing ♪
♪ Which you're missing so ♪
♪ 'Cause it's Christmas time ♪
♪ You should be here with me ♪
♪ Fa la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la... ♪
Hah! Keeping my hours, are you?
Is this part of your bid
for partnership?
No, I just woke up happy,
that's all.
Oh. For the final?
Nah. About a lot of things.
Oh. Oh, I, I like this.
This is fresh and sophisticated.
Can we get a photo,
uh, for our portfolio?
No, I can't, because I didn't
actually design it myself.
Well, then, who did?
Poppy Benson and I
made it together.
Poppy?
Mm-hmm.
How did that come about?
I think it's called a...
a date, Blair.
- A date?
- Yeah, it's this great thing.
People find each other
attractive,
they go out, they grab a meal,
they get to know each other.
And arrange flowers together?
Pretty much. Ta-dah.
Listen, I gotta put this
on my desk.
I'll swing by your office and
we'll talk about that banquet
in New York.
- Morning, Marie.
- Good morning.
- What do you think?
- Ooh.
You meets cool.
Oh, I like that.
Great, I'll hashtag it
and put it on the Petals page.
Okay, so if we could just
multiply this by thirty,
and then, add in twelve or so
large arrangements,
we've got a party.
And it's about T-minus 26 hours
until the first center piece
hits the table.
Are you ready
for an all-nighter?
If you're willing
to meet my terms.
- Hit me.
- Okay.
One of your father's
famous fruit cakes
with extra-green cherries,
and I'm gonna need
a lot of caffeine.
Okay, well, we have plenty
of espresso in the back.
And I will put the request in
with my dad right now.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
So...
no more playing coy, Ms. Benson.
I wanna know all about
Mr. Covington Designs.
He's, he's, uh, actually
a really nice guy.
Boring.
Skip to the good stuff.
Okay. He, uh, he smells
like cedar and vanilla.
Okay. We're getting warmer.
And when he puts his arms
around me,
I feel like a marshmallow
melting in hot cocoa.
We have a winner.
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
This is when you get
your happy back.
- What?
- All the happy you give away?
It's finally coming back to you.
Okay. We have work to do,
let's go.
Okay, we're on it.
One hundred and forty-five
eucalyptus fronds
cut and trimmed.
Check.
Now, only 145 more to go.
I was just gonna leave
for the night.
Don't you think
it's a little dim in here?
You can't do your best work
if you have to squint to see.
Nah, the atmosphere
helps me focus.
Your focus is something I've
wanted to speak with you about.
Is there a problem?
Well, I know that you've, uh,
become fond of that Poppy girl.
- Yes.
- So, I'll just be blunt.
When are you ever anything but?
She's a direct competitor.
So I think you might consider
what her motivation is
for becoming friendly with you.
What are you trying to say?
I don't want you to
lose your edge...
just because you've become
smitten with some girl
who could just be trying
to distract you from winning.
Look, Blair, I know you like
to be in control of everything...
You have a lot riding on this,
Garrett.
We both do.
You know, my personal life
is not a subsidiary
of Covington Designs.
I just have your best interest
at heart.
Well, I'm not so sure.
Well, it's late,
and you, you're tired,
so, uh...
call it a night soon
and tomorrow, everything
will be fresh and new.
How so?
Goodnight.
Okay.
Just move that box.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Over there. Okay, great.
Excuse me, are you the famous
Poppy from Poppy's Petals?
Maybe. Who's asking?
Breakfast croissant
delivery service.
I mean, you can't
properly arrange
flowers on an empty stomach.
It's peanut butter and jelly.
It's my favorite.
How did you know?
- Lucky guess.
- This look delicious.
- Thank you.
- Hi, I'm Natalie. Remember?
We met. Okay, we gotta go.
I know this looks delicious.
Put it down.
We gotta go. We've got flowers
wilting in there.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
Um...
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Uh... See you later, right?
Yeah. I'll see you there.
Okay.
- Bye, Natalie.
- Bye!
- You left the backdoor... Yeah.
- Oh. Could you? Thank you.
You don't have to wait,
we'll be fine.
I'm gonna call Joe.
Just pop the hood.
I'll, I'll check it.
Does he know about...
Do you know anything about cars?
Well, I know
Edna's irreplaceable.
You remember her name.
I don't know what all I can do,
but at least I'll take a look.
Okay. Nat, could you call Joe?
Yeah, I'm on it.
I can't believe
this is happening.
I don't know
what the problem is.
Well, with Edna, the question
is, "What isn't the problem?"
If we don't leave for Tiffany's
party now, we're gonna miss it.
Well, Joe said he can't be here
for an hour and a half.
I think I have a solution
pulling up right now.
Garrett, what is this?
Okay. Today, we're giving
Cranky Edna a rest.
Come help me unload these,
uh, arrangements.
You don't wanna miss the party,
do you?
- No.
- Nice.
- Okay, come on.
- Okay, okay.
Thanks, buddy.
I think that's it. We did it.
And we finished a little early
which leaves me time to freshen
up for my holiday date tonight.
- Ooh!
- I mean, that is...
If you don't need me anymore.
Nope. All the heavy-lifting
is done.
I'm gonna stick around and wait
for the party to begin.
I want Tiffany to tell me
how much she loves it.
Oh, she's gonna love it.
And these smell amazing.
This eucalyptus
was the perfect touch.
Yeah. Okay, scoot.
But don't stay out too late.
I need you fresh for
the competition in the morning.
Oh. I was born fresh.
Thank you.
- The flowers are lovely, dear.
- Thank you.
Yeah, I'm really happy
how everything turned out.
And you look nice, as well.
Well, thank you.
I mean, you look amazing.
I could never wear
anything like that.
I would undoubtedly
spill something on it.
I suppose it does take
a little grace
or something to pull it off.
Aren't they
a picture of perfection?
- Huh?
- Garrett and Tiffany.
- What do you mean?
- Well...
I mean, supposedly,
they're just friends right now.
But everyone knows that there's
unrequited flame between them
that could go off
at any moment and...
I mean, why shouldn't it?
They've been so close
for so many years.
Not to mention,
they look perfect together.
Poppy, dear, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, I, um...
just wanna make sure everything
looks perfect for the party.
Oh, it'll be wonderful.
Everything happens
as it should and...
and someday soon, those two
will realize it, as well.
You know, I know that we did not
start off on the right foot.
But I assure you,
as I've been there,
it's not wise for a woman
to give her heart to a man
who's really pining
for someone else.
Right.
Oh, oh...
Oh...
Could someone get her a tissue?
- Oh, my... Um...
- Oh, Tiffany, Tiffany, look.
Oh, Poppy. Eucalyptus?
My grandmother
is horribly allergic.
- Excuse me.
- I didn't tell you.
What do I do?
We're on it. We're on it.
Okay. I think that's all of it.
What else can I do?
No, you just go back
to your party.
- I think you've done enough.
- What's wrong?
I told you
I was using eucalyptus.
Are you gonna try and tell me
you didn't know
that your girlfriend's
grandmother would literally
keel over at the sight
of a eucalyptus branch?
My girlfriend?
Oh, it's not a secret.
Blair told me your past
and your future.
Wait, Blair told you
what exactly?
Don't worry about it, Garrett.
I knew I shouldn't
have trusted you.
It was quite clear
this entire time
you have been stringing me
all along just like your boss.
Okay, Poppy,
you've got it all wrong.
Apparently, I do.
Poppy...
Are you feeling better, grandma?
I am, sweetheart. Thank you.
Well, bless Tiffany's heart.
But this is what happens
when you use
an inexperienced vendor.
♪ Chill to the bones... ♪
Hey, Blair.
- Can I, uh...
- Oh.
Why did you tell Poppy that
Tiffany's my girlfriend?
Girlfriend? I never said
anything of the sort.
Is, is winning that important
that you're willing
to hurt me to do it?
I want you to succeed, Garrett.
None of this is for me.
I think you're scared
because she's good.
You're better.
Well, that remains to be seen,
but you know what,
I'm willing to let
the judges decide.
This is silly.
You know, we can discuss
this tomorrow, Garrett,
privately.
We had a deal, Blair.
If I lose, I sign on
for five more years.
But I know I can win this thing
without your... tactics.
So, please,
let me do this on my own.
Fine. I'm a spectator.
I yield to your endeavors. Okay?
Oh, look,
it's Governor Stratton.
I will go say hello.
♪ This Christmas Eve ♪
♪ Why'd it turn out differently? ♪
♪ Now something's missing ♪
♪ Something's missing ♪
♪ Oh something's missing ♪
♪ It's not the stocking ♪
♪ It's not the tree ♪
♪ Lights of green ♪
♪ Red and blue ♪
♪ It's not the time ♪
♪ It's not the roof ♪
♪ It's you you you ♪
♪ It's you ♪
Oh, Joe.
So did I.
♪ Something's missing... ♪
Poppy?
Poppy, it's dad. Are you okay?
I made you peanut butter
and jelly toast.
Let me try.
Hey, Poppy.
It's Natalie.
Come on, you gotta get up.
It's show time.
We need to get to the finals.
I'm not going anywhere.
Edna's not moving
and I'm not moving.
It's over.
Poppy Hyacinth Benson,
what would your grandmother say
if she saw you
giving up like this?
What would your mother say?
I gave someone an allergic
reaction with my flowers.
Eucalyptus, of all things.
Who's allergic to eucalyptus?
Poppy, please let us in.
No. I can do everything
from here.
I got a cell phone,
I got a hot-spot...
Yeah, well you're gonna be
in the hot-seat
if you don't get it together
and get ready.
Come on!
Hold on.
Ugh...
One, two, three.
No!
I don't have to go anywhere.
I have rights.
Poppy...
you-you're down but not out.
So, get up, get dressed,
young lady,
and let's go win this final.
No, dad, the structure
to my displays
don't fit in any cars,
and Edna...
Dad, please don't open
the window.
I don't need any vitamin-D.
Would you quit feeling sorry
for yourself for one second
and look out the window?
We got a surprise for you.
Merry Christmas, sleepyhead.
Why is Joe here?
Natalie called him this morning.
Why?
Just get out here already.
- I'll show you.
- Ugh...
- Come on.
Let's do it for Edna.
For Edna.
Yes!
Looks like Poppy's Petals
is a no-show.
- That's too bad.
- Oh, please.
You nearly buckled
under the pressure, too.
I did not.
Well, looks like
your girl's a no-show.
I'm so sorry, Garrett.
But at least now you're
practically a shoo-in to win.
We all know that
Roses Are Red Florals
has nothing
on Covington Designs.
That's true.
Can't you at least be
a little bit excited?
Oh...
Cheery good morning
to all our designers and teams.
Designers, teams,
would you please come down
to the podium?
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Of course, we have a short bit
of business before we start.
I'd like to start by thanking
all of our sponsors today
who are making this possible.
Thank you.
Garrett, where are you going?
What took you so long?
If you're not in the booth
at the time
that clock starts,
you forfeit the competition.
I am perfectly fine carrying
this by myself, Garrett.
Let me help you carry this,
Poppy, please.
Oh, come on.
For once, will you let
somebody help you?
Look, Tiffany's not
my girlfriend.
She's never been my girlfriend,
okay?
We've just been friends forever.
How am I supposed
to believe you?
- Let me help you with that.
- No, it's fine.
I mean, would
I really be down here
dying under this giant tea cup
if I wanted it any other way?
I suppose not.
Thank you for helping me again.
You're welcome.
But why? I thought you wanted
to win this competition.
I did. I do. I just...
If I'm gonna win, I wanna do it
fair and square.
And if I lose...
I want it to be to you.
You know, I would kiss you
if I could move.
Well, here, let me help.
Oh...
- Everything okay down there?
- Yeah.
Mm, two turtle love doves.
Don't we have a final to get to?
- You ready?
- Let's do this.
Oh, dear, it looks as if
we're missing Miss Benson
and Mr. Hurley.
Ah! It appears that
the winners will be...
- We're here.
- Wait, wait, wait, we're here!
Cutting it close!
- We're here.
I can see this is going to be
a very exciting day!
Okay, finalists, are you ready?
Then let the finals begin!
Okay, guys. Sorry, I'm late.
I need few things.
Fake snow... Real snow.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Now, let's break this open.
Garrett, I thought you wanted
to win this thing?
Or maybe you want to spend
another five years with me?
You know, there are worse things
than losing, Blair.
It's Christmas time. Remember?
And what's important
this time of year is that
everybody gets a chance
to-to work hard
at something greater,
to find hope in-in things
that are out of their control,
to, to realize that, you know,
lending a helping hand
is far greater
than any cash prize.
I remember, I remember when
you thought you were nobody
and you asked
for my help that day.
I just miss the girl who...
trusted in people enough
to ask for a helping hand.
Anyway, I got to
get back to work
because Blair Covington
has to win, right?
Designers!
You have two hours!
Okay, Pops, it's time to make
your Christmas wish come true.
Yes.
Okay. So, whole right here.
And the eyes here
and then the...
Designers, you have
one hour left!
Huh?
Designers, you have
one minute left.
- Blair! What are you doing?
- Oh, no. The clock.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Oh, gosh, uh...
Find me some, uh, floral wire.
Everything's already packed up.
Just some string or anything.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Yikes. Okay. Uh...
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
three, two, one!
Designers,
step away from your designs.
Let the judging begin.
Thank you.
Did you see the smiles
on their faces?
You did it, Pop.
No, wedid it.
Thank you guys so much.
It just looks so lifelike.
Makes me wanna
dip a cookie in it.
What?
They had Christmas cookies
on the refreshment table,
so I grabbed a few.
Cute. Thanks.
They should give you
extra points
for helping the competition out.
No, I had to. He's been helping
me on numerous amounts of times.
I felt like I needed to.
Well, your grandmother
and your mother
would be very,
very proud of you.
Thank you.
I just want you guys to know
I really appreciate it,
and that...
I mean that from
the bottom of my heart.
Hey, are you kidding?
I just came here
for the cookies.
Seriously,
you guys are the best.
And no matter what happens,
I just want you to know
that I wouldn't do this
any differently.
I just want to be with you guys.
- And especially me.
- Yes.
Okay. Team Poppy,
let's bring it in.
We will meet back here
in exactly one hour
to announce the winners.
And in the meantime, please,
enjoy the refreshments.
That's what they're for.
Will all the finalists
please move down to the stage?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's been a day
of ups and downs,
fierce competition,
and, of course,
the magic of the season.
I, for one,
could not be more proud
to be a member of
the Santa Mesa Floral Community.
And how about all of you?
But enough of
my emotional gushes.
Let's announce our runners up,
shall we?
All right, in third place,
Audrey and Phil Wilson
of Roses Are Red Florals.
Congratulations.
And if the two remaining
finalists,
will please come forward.
Which one of these two
incredible designers
will win this year's
competition?
I really do wish you the best.
You, too.
Ah!
And the winner is...
Poppy Benson...
of Poppy's Petals!
Wonderful! Congratulations!
I'm sorry I didn't win,
Blair, I...
- I know you're disappointed.
- No, no, dear.
No. I am so proud of what
you've done here today.
I really am.
And you will always be
my winner.
I am so sorry
for how badly I behaved.
Good, because I'm gonna be
around for a while longer.
Five years with or without
the promise of a partnership.
Yeah, no.
Now that you've had
a taste of being in charge,
you would be insufferable
and I couldn't possibly
keep you around.
I, I don't understand.
I think it's time that you
submit your resignation
to Covington, for good.
- So you're, you're firing me?
- No.
I'm telling you to go off and be
the second-best florist
in Santa Mesa.
Well, can I keep
all my long-term clients?
Thank you for teaching me
so well.
Yeah. Maybe too well.
Yes.
You know, I guess,
maybe what we've learned
is that a little healthy
competition never hurt anybody.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, thank you.
I suppose I should go
be gracious
and congratulate the woman
who beat Covington
finally after all these years.
And I'll see you both
at next year's competition.
You're still number one
in our book.
Thanks, squad.
I just wanted to offer you
my sincere
congratulations, Miss Benson.
Uh... Um, thank you.
Well, I was wondering
if I could speak with you
in private for a moment, dear?
- I've got your back.
- Thank you.
I haven't exactly been, uh,
kind to you throughout
this competition, dear.
Not exactly.
But that's because
I thought you were
trying to distract Garrett
from winning.
No, you're wrong.
Either way,
I owe you an apology.
Apology accepted.
I'm too much of a fan
of yours not to, you know.
Thank you, dear.
And you know, I'm not
the only one with a fan here.
Garrett really does care
for you, and I'm just so sorry
that I...
that I just deceived you
into thinking that he doesn't.
No, that's okay.
I feel like
I already knew he did.
I was just, I don't know,
too insecure
to believe it until now.
Okay, good.
Do me a favor
and tell your friends
I was just awful with you.
I do have a reputation
to uphold.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, sweetie.
I'm so stinkin' excited for us!
Wait, does this mean I can add
Award-Winning Florist
to my resume?
Yes!
Hey, you.
Congratulations.
Looks like that multitasking
finally paid off.
Thank you.
Is it stupid that I'm also
incredibly sad you didn't win?
No, you're not.
But that's okay.
Can I be both?
You know, in a way, I feel like
I kind of did win today.
Oh, yeah? Why?
Well, because I finally got you
under the mistletoe.
♪ There were just stars in the sky ♪
♪ Until you came along ♪
♪ And they started to shine ♪
♪ I never realized ♪
♪ Just what I was missing ♪
♪ There were just lights on a tree ♪
♪ Till they turned to a spotlight ♪
♪ Shining down on you and me ♪
♪ I never thought I can feel ♪
♪ So in love but ♪
♪ I just wanna fall into
your arms this Christmas ♪
Whoa! Look who it is.
Hey!
Merry Christmas!
Lovely.
Beautiful.
Thank you. Hi.
Hello.
- And a Merry Christmas.
- Oh!
Would you like an eggnog?
♪ I used to agree with the Grinch ♪
♪ Till you showed me just
how beautiful Christmas is ♪
♪ Now you're the top of my list ♪
♪ Each December ♪
♪ I just wanna fall into
your arms this Christmas ♪
♪ I just wanna celebrate
the gift you've given ♪
♪ You opened my eyes ♪
♪ And brought down my guard ♪
♪ I let you in and you unwrapped my heart ♪
♪ You're the star on my tree ♪
♪ You make Christmas complete ♪
♪ Fa la la ♪
♪ La la la laa ♪
♪ La la laa ♪
♪ You make Christmas complete ♪